Glass pipe + ashes + dose of dmt ('about a third of a standard vial') + flame = :
I inhaled very deeply.
The burning DMT smelled like shit.
I immediately felt a tingly, and the whole room became soft and shiny.
I noticed that I could intensely hear all the static of the atmosphere surrounding me.
I felt like I need to be wearing a hood, but instead reach for a blanket and put it over me.
I said, 'I just need to hang out under this blanket for a bit guys' out loud.
I closed my eyes.
There was a lawn and a tree.
And a box.
Red bricks came out of the box's mouth and began to build a pyramid.
There's a tree on the left side of me, but I could only see half of it; it looked really pixilated, like the mooninites from aqua teen hunger force.
However, most of the scenery reminded me of the art in Maurice Sendak's where the wild things are.
I tilted my head up and could see the sky.
I said 'the sky is beautiful - space is fucked.
' out loud.
I opened my eyes.
I closed them again.
I was sitting next to a river, it looked like a mosaic of pastel gel pens on black paper.
I said, 'water is amazing; I love water' out loud.
A million blightly-coloured rocks that resemble skittles rose rising out of the sand and formed different kaleidescopic pictures.
The rocks started to move in a tube up and up and I kept looking watching them disappear into the sky until the tube quickly jerks back towards me and it was a dragon who flied by me.
The rest of his body turned into different little streams and peak, so it appeared to me a volcano spewing purple and blue liquid.
I followed it to the right and see myself: the blue and purple are the colours of the blanket surrounding me.
I opened my eyes because I didn't want to see anymore.
It was fucking fantastic.